

East Rutherford, NJ 07073

□ +1 (201) 566-1970 | ■ nataliemfreay@gmail.com | ■ nataliefreay

Summary ____

Great team player and a confident leader with 3 years various supervisor experience. Goal oriented and driven individual who can accomplish tasks with little to no supervision. Experienced in inventory management and ensure clean productive running of multiple operations. Looking to start a career in the medical field. Bilingual and eager to help people with a plethora of communications experience in multiple backgrounds.

Work Experience __

American Dream 2020 - Present

MERCHANDISE & OPERATIONS SUPERVISOR

E. Rutherford, NJ

- Oversee inventory for 100+ unique products
- Oversee 7 stores and 5 kiosks
- Stock, replenish, and organize inventory in the warehouse, storage rooms, stores, and kiosks
- Managing and allocating breaks for 25+ employees
- Call dispatch for money drops
- Assist an average of 100+ customers per day in finding or selecting items, and providing recommendations
- · Aid Spanish-speaking 20+ customers per day
- Authorize 5 exchanges and refunds per day

Delaware North 2019 - 2021

RETAIL SUPERVISOR E. Rutherford, NJ

- Oversaw 2 stores at MetLife Stadium
- Managed 3 employees per store
- Replenished stock of 20+ products
- Stock and stylize merchandising
- Reconciled cash drawer at the end of night, accounting errors and resolving discrepancies
- · Assisted an average of 50+ customers per game day in finding or selecting items, and providing recommendations

Century 21 Department Store

2019 - 2020

ASSET PROTECTION SUPERVISOR

Paramus/Elizabeth/E. Rutherford, NJ

- Assigned and scheduled 5 specialists across 4 in-store locations
- · Acted as a liaison between Asset Protections and upper management, providing summarizing and providing daily event logs
- Kept detailed documentation of 5+ audits for 3 locations every month
- Monitored 30+ cameras (CCTV)
- Operated store switchboard, provided courteous and knowledgeable assistance to 20+ calls per day

My Little University 2018 - 2019

LEAD TEACHEREast Rutherford, NJ

- · Maintained strict records of newborns and toddler's habits (physical activities & diet) by using the Daily Connect app
- Oversaw the newborn room with 20+ children ranging between 7 weeks old to 15 months
- Responsible for 12 children ranging between 16 to 24 months
- Performed meal and bottle preparations
- Taught New Jersey's Department of Education recommended curriculum (The Creative Curriculum System)

Skills

Languages English (native), Spanish (fluent)

Software MS Word, MS PowerPoint, MS Excel, POS System (Shopify), Nexus Systems (Invoices) **Personal** Attention to Detail, Customer Service, Team Leadership, Problem Solving/Adaptability

Education _

Bergen Community College (Paramus, NJ)

2020 - Current

Montclair University (Montclair, NJ)

2015 - 2016

Hobbies